Gershenfeld, Walter and Gladys Arbitration Papers 6344
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Publications, 1943-1983 (Box 11)
  - 1954-1963 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 1943-1953 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Publications, 1983-2010 and undated (Box 12)
  - No Date (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2010 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 2008 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2007 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 2002 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 1989 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 1986 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 1985 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 1984 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)